werockyourweb.com 2019-08-16

# Privacy Policy – We Rock Your Web

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit WeRockYourWeb.com?**

When ordering or registering on WeRockYourWeb.com, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you:

  * Subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on WeRockYourWeb.com.
  * Provide us with feedback on our products or services.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries).

 **How do we protect your information?**

  * We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
  * We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.
  * We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

 **We use cookies to:**

  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, It won’t affect the user’s experience.

 **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce WeRockYourWeb.com policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of WeRockYourWeb.com and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by [Google’s Advertising Principles](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en). They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on WeRockYourWeb.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to WeRockYourWeb.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

 **We have implemented the following:**

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

 **Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the [Google Ad Settings page](https://adssettings.google.com/). Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the [Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

[CalOPPA](http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/) is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared.

 **According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**

  * Users can visit WeRockYourWeb.com anonymously.
  * Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information:

  * By [contacting us](https://www.werockyourweb.com/contact/)

 **How does WeRockYourWeb.com handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

 **Does WeRockYourWeb.com allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking.

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

 **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify you via email

  * Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

 **We collect your email address in order to:**

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

 **To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

 **If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can[contact us](https://www.werockyourweb.com/contact/)**.

Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from

  * ALL correspondence.

 **Online Comment, Forum And Disclosure Policy**

WeRockYourWeb.com welcomes reader feedback to its online content, but it is not responsible for the information contained in reader comments. We reserve the right to reject, edit or delete comments in full or in part at any time.

Comments should not be abusive, libelous or in bad taste. They should not contain vulgar language. We prefer comments that express an opinion rather than ones that deal in personalities.

While we strive to keep our research as up to date and accurate as possible, due to the dynamic nature of the industry, we will occasionally make errors or fail to keep content current. If you find inaccuracies in our content, please [contact us](https://www.werockyourweb.com/contact/) and we will do our best to resolve the errors as soon as possible.

We reserve the right to reproduce information sent to us via our [contact form](https://www.werockyourweb.com/contact/) and social media, in full or in part, on WeRockYourWeb.com, regardless of the medium used.

As a rule, we will not intentionally disclose any personal identification information about you as an individual user (such as, for example, your full name, street address, telephone number, or e-mail address) to any third party without having received your permission. Please note that if you give out personal information online “for example, through an article comment or forum topic ” that information can be collected and used by third parties. Although we strive to protect our users’ privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of information you post in these forums. You disclose such information at your own risk.

We have the following exceptions to this disclosure policy: We will release specific information about you or your account to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute or court order. We will also release specific information in special cases, such as if there is an attempted breach of the security of WeRockYourWeb.com, or a physical threat to you or others.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may [contact us](https://www.werockyourweb.com/contact/).

 _Last Edited on 2018-05-24_
